Tomorrow morning the superintendent is ready the condition of the machines is covered in
blood
and in the morning you will pay with the video welcome to my channel Gyan
Pizza this video
so there is something that I want to tell you guys
why the video is not coming why the
video is not there look I had an
accident on the night of Kali Puja and
falling at the speed of friend Akhtar so you
can understand what happened to me on the road nothing
much happened to me in other words
everything happened to me mostly here let me
show you the photos you guys see the photos these are the first photos
these are all the photos of what happened to me
I am fine now whatever they are I am fine I was
not fine before also I am fine it was
around 30s it was happening then we were
coming from Islampur towards Panji Pada towards home at
that time I did not have any sleep at all
we were in the car
one of my brothers was driving I was in the middle
my friend was sitting at the back there were
three monkeys on the scooter and my brother was
driving there was no air in the car the
remote got broken in the boat after dropping the car
whatever air was there  He got out and
started pulling the wheels off the car, then he
dropped the car and fell asleep right on the road, we all
went here and there 7023 fell on the back, the
condition of the car was completely standing but I
can go to the market, there is 125 written
on the side, what can I say for 125, the sticker is
worn out, I am not able to find it on the road,
I will tell you the condition of the car now, you will
understand what kind of
accident it was,
yesterday morning the superintendent was here, the condition of the instruments is covered with
blood, it is
fine at home, it is finished,
and you can see this thing,
look at Hisar, it is
completely dangerous, it fell and got lost,
where did it fall,
and what, and this one here is lying on the edge, it is
completely dangerous, I do
n't know what to do with it, let's do
something, let's start it, see what
happens, and did it not come,
where did the phone come, it had also fallen,
nothing is happening, call
Ajay,
hey
Supine Ali, after 20 days the car started, the
sound has gone wrong, call Ajay
[Music] Do it
Ajay,
I am alive, this is my luck, I mean I am
alive, otherwise I would have died. On this day, a
truck was coming from behind, we among the truck drivers
saw that we fell, so the truck
driver slowed down the vehicle and stopped, the truck came back on the
road, but the road here is
not good for us, it is a big one, the biggest one, Bahrod, we have a
lot of problems, it is
only for the bus stand, you know, the condition of the vehicle has become
very bad, we will do it right now, I do
n't have any money to do this, my
wife has given me only 5,000 rupees,
tell me, do it in this, how many times should I give
you the money for the house, I mean, this is a small
way to do it, everyone is fed up, tell me only,
a few days ago I got my engine repaired
and again an accident happened at home, so scold me
completely, let's say, no
one is bothered.